# Nandishwar C

#### **Lead Analyst**

Having 7.5 years of experience in developing and leading highly scalable applications and services in a cloud operating environment. Career objective is to stay up to par with technologies, creatively and analytically, by learning and experimenting with emerging technologies and apply the same on Product Implementation, User Experience, and building reporting/Analytics.

nandigowda094@gmail.com

8861442218

Bengaluru, India

in www.linkedin.com/in/nandishwar-c-20b942169

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Lead Analyst

# LSEG (London Stock Exchange Group)

02/2023 - Present, Responsibilities

Bengaluru

- Lead, Drive and Collaborate with Business on Designing and Implementing aspects including requirement gathering, effective solution designing and Go-Live for a large group.
- Contribute to **Technically designing solution** and involve in development of POC/Prototype for many business requirements that reduced working hours spent on the implementation.
- Taking accountability to ensure the product is performing high levels of customer satisfaction, and configured the designs and implementations following the best practices which included effective usage of ASANA (Modern ways of working) and JIRA.
- Working on implementing a Platform for a multiple Risk and Compliance frameworks which included Business Continuity Management (BCM), Third Party Management (TPM), Regulatory Engagements (REM), Operational Risk and Compliance Management (ORM & CMP) and Policy and Document Management System.

# Senior Risk Advisory **KPMG Global Services**

10/2021 - 02/2023,

Bengaluru

Responsibilities

- Collaborate with Customer, Business Analysts and Technical teams on implementation aspects including requirement validation, solution.
- Design innovative new products with focus on exposing key competitive advantages.
- Involved in following exercises: 1. Software estimation exercises 2. Application implementation and validation 3. Application design and code reviews 4. Debugging and defect resolution 5. Establishing and maintaining clear, concise, and complete design documentation that is modern, maintainable, and transferrable.
- Worked on Audit management, Risk and Control Management

# Senior Software Engineer

JOY IT Solutions 01/2020 - 10/2021,

Bengaluru

Responsibilities

- Efficient in multitasking and taking full ownership of delivering applications including end to end development, delivery & post production support.
- Responsible for configuring underlying architecture of GRC Products as well as involved in developing custom GRC solution for customer requirements. Involved in complex integrations from various back-end services and databases.
- Involved in Internal IT Audit, Risk Assessments and Manage control for several clients.

# CERTIFICATIONS AND TRAININGS

- Trained on ServiceNow: ServiceNow Fundamentals on Demand, Third-party Risk Management Fundamentals (Vancouver).
- Certification: Nanodegree Front End Web Developer, UDACITY

### **KEY SKILLS**



# **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Engineering Telecommunication** KSIT, VTU

2012 - 2016.

72%

### **ORGANIZATIONS**

- LSEG (02/2023 Present) Lead Analyst
- KPMG Global Services (10/2021 02/2023)
- JOY IT Solutions (01/2020 10/2021) Partner at MSI (SMTS)
- Infosys (12/2016 01/2020) Partner at MSI (MTS)

#### SOFT SKILLS

